<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tinh Truong&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.tinhtruong.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tinh Truong&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 22:15:50 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.tinhtruong.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Highlighting Text With Lucene Highlighter</title>
      <link>https://blog.tinhtruong.me/post/highlighting-text-with-lucene-highlighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 22:15:50 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tinhtruong.me/post/highlighting-text-with-lucene-highlighter/</guid>
      <description>I have a chance to use Lucene (3.6.0) to implement a full-text search in one of my recent projects. One of the requirements is to highlight the matched text in the result. The highlighted text should be displayed in the whole paragraph (not just a small text fragment). Here is my snippet to achieve this:
private String getHighlightedField(Query query, Analyzer analyzer, String fieldName, String fieldValue) throws IOException, InvalidTokenOffsetsException { Formatter formatter = new SimpleHTMLFormatter(&amp;quot;&amp;lt;span class=\&amp;quot;MatchedText\&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;quot;); QueryScorer queryScorer = new QueryScorer(query); Highlighter highlighter = new Highlighter(formatter, queryScorer); highlighter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compiling JNotify on Ubuntu 64bit</title>
      <link>https://blog.tinhtruong.me/post/compiling-jnotify-on-ubuntu-64bit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 22:52:56 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tinhtruong.me/post/compiling-jnotify-on-ubuntu-64bit/</guid>
      <description>In my recent project, I have a need to monitor a directory for changes such as a new file created, modified or deleted. Surprisingly, JDK (up to JDK 6) does not have APIs to do that! JDK 7 does support it out of the box but I am stuck with the version 6.
After looking around for an existing solution, I finally found that jNotify seems to fit the need. It supports all the three major platforms (Windows, Linux, and MacOS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring JNDI Mail Session in Tomcat</title>
      <link>https://blog.tinhtruong.me/post/configuring-jndi-mail-session-in-tomcat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 21:42:15 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tinhtruong.me/post/configuring-jndi-mail-session-in-tomcat/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just joined a project as a freelancer to customize a commercial e-commerce solution (so let called it EP). OOTB, the email sending of EP does not support authentication, which is a weird thing for such a cool product like that. Actually, EP does declare an JNDI mail session in the context, but in the code they don&amp;rsquo;t use it. With the source code of EP in hand, things get much easier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FPT Will Have a Mirror for Arch Soon</title>
      <link>https://blog.tinhtruong.me/post/fpt-will-have-a-mirror-for-arch-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 21:54:48 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tinhtruong.me/post/fpt-will-have-a-mirror-for-arch-soon/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve switched to ArchLinux from Fedora a couple of months ago and I really miss the mirror of Fedora on FPT (my current ISP). A few days ago, I wrote an email to ask the FPT mirrors admin to add a mirror for ArchLinux to their mirror systems. Here is what I wrote (in Vietnamese):
 Gởi Admin mirror của FPT.
Arch Linux là một distro khá phổ biến hiện nay, ArchLinux đang đứng trong top 20 distro phổ biến theo Distrowatch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>